<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Garden Fence on Garden Fence - Fediverse Blocklist</title>
    <link>https://gardenfence.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Garden Fence on Garden Fence - Fediverse Blocklist</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://gardenfence.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Participation</title>
      <link>https://gardenfence.github.io/participation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 14:42:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gardenfence.github.io/participation/</guid>
      <description>Reference Servers As of Sep. 2024, servers used as references for filtering are no longer listed. This is primarily due to the time and effort required to find suitable reference servers that are also willing to be publicly listed as such, making it extremely difficult and time consuming to replace servers removed from the list.
Blocks from reference servers are now only used to filter down the sunny.garden blocklist to include the most widely blocked &amp;ldquo;worst of the worst&amp;rdquo; domains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://gardenfence.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gardenfence.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Maintained by @brook@sunny.garden.
Follow @gardenfence@sunny.garden for notification of updates or other important changes to the list.
The information on this site is provided on a best effort basis in the hope that others may find it useful, but without warranty of any kind. Use the information provided here at your own risk.
THE website IS PROVIDED “AS IS”, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
